module.exports = [
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the actor who played the character "Borat" in the movie "Borat: Cultural Learnings of America for Make Benefit Glorious Nation of Kazakhstan" (2006)?',
    correctAnswer: "Sacha Baron Cohen",
    wrongAnswers: ["Jim Carrey", "Adam Sandler", "Ben Stiller"],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "The Hangover" (2009)?',
    correctAnswer: "Todd Phillips",
    wrongAnswers: ["Judd Apatow", "Wes Anderson", "Martin Scorsese"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Will Ferrell play a character named Ron Burgundy?",
    correctAnswer: "Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy (2004)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Step Brothers (2008)",
      "The Other Guys (2010)",
      "Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby (2006)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Eddie Murphy in the movie "Coming to America" (1988)?',
    correctAnswer: "Prince Akeem Joffer",
    wrongAnswers: ["Clarence", "Axel Foley", "Billy Ray Valentine"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which movie features a character named "The Dude" played by Jeff Bridges?',
    correctAnswer: "The Big Lebowski (1998)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Superbad (2007)",
      "Napoleon Dynamite (2004)",
      "Bridesmaids (2011)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who played the character of Michael Scott in the TV series "The Office" (US)?',
    correctAnswer: "Steve Carell",
    wrongAnswers: ["John Krasinski", "Rainn Wilson", "Ed Helms"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In which movie does Jim Carrey play a character who can only say "yes"?',
    correctAnswer: "Yes Man (2008)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Mask (1994)",
      "Bruce Almighty (2003)",
      "Dumb and Dumber (1994)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the movie "Mean Girls" (2004)?',
    correctAnswer: "Mark Waters",
    wrongAnswers: ["Paul Feig", "Amy Heckerling", "John Hughes"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Jonah Hill and Channing Tatum as undercover cops in a high school?",
    correctAnswer: "21 Jump Street (2012)",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Superbad (2007)",
      "Pineapple Express (2008)",
      "This Is the End (2013)",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the character played by Mike Myers in the "Austin Powers" movies?',
    correctAnswer: "Austin Powers",
    wrongAnswers: ["Dr. Evil", "Fat Bastard", "Mini-Me"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Bridesmaids" (2011), which character is secretly in love with the groom, Lillian\'s fiance?',
    correctAnswer: "Megan",
    wrongAnswers: ["Annie", "Becca", "Rita"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Dumb and Dumber", what is the name of the briefcase that Harry and Lloyd are trying to return?',
    correctAnswer: "Mr. Yellow",
    wrongAnswers: ["Mr. Orange", "Mr. Blue", "Mr. Pink"],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy" (2004), what is the name of the news team led by Ron Burgundy?',
    correctAnswer: "The Channel 4 News Team",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "The Action News Team",
      "The Eyewitness News Team",
      "The Network News Team",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the movie "The Big Lebowski" (1998), what is the nickname of the character played by Jeff Bridges?',
    correctAnswer: "The Dude",
    wrongAnswers: ["The Big Lebowski", "Walter Sobchak", "Donny Kerabatsos"],
  },
];
